<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Meta on RoboTamer </title>
    <link>http://www.robotamer.com/groups/meta.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author>Dennis T Kaplan</author>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2013, Dennis T Kaplan; all rights reserved.</rights>
    <updated>2008-01-01 00:00:00 &#43;0000 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>My little space on the net</title>
      <link>http://www.robotamer.com/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Dennis T Kaplan</author>
      <guid>http://www.robotamer.com/about.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;right&#34;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;/static/img/robotamer.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Logo&#34; /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
Here you will find mostly documentation for some of the things I have coded.&lt;br /&gt;
Improvements and/or bug reports are encouraged.&lt;br /&gt;
Go ahead feel right at home, at the top is the main menu pointing to each project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless otherwise specified within the code, most everything you can find here is MIT licensed.
The link to the generic license is in the Meta menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website has been created with &lt;a href=&#34;http://github.com/spf13/hugo&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt; a Go program that converts
markdown files to a complete website.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copyright</title>
      <link>http://www.robotamer.com/license.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Dennis T Kaplan</author>
      <guid>http://www.robotamer.com/license.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2012 The GoTamer Authors. All rights reserved.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neither the name of GoTamer nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
