<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Google on RoboTamer </title>
    <link>http://www.robotamer.com/tags/google.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author>Dennis T Kaplan</author>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2013, Dennis T Kaplan; all rights reserved.</rights>
    <updated>2011-07-08 22:00:25 &#43;0000 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google, the most dangerous monopoly ever</title>
      <link>http://www.robotamer.com/blog/2011-07-08-google-the-most-dangerous-monopoly-ever.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 22:00:25 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Dennis T Kaplan</author>
      <guid>http://www.robotamer.com/blog/2011-07-08-google-the-most-dangerous-monopoly-ever.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I use almost all Google services ranging from search engine, over Gmail, Calendar, Android and Google Voice all the way to Webmaster Tools and Google Analytics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you combine all that data, I think that Google may know me better then I know my self, and that is starting to make me nerves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I think that Google is a great company, the services provided are excellent, and I don&amp;rsquo;t have a reason to believe that my data has been compromised. I just feel uncomfortable with one single entity having so much information about me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on my own experience, I believe that Google is starting to become a dangers monopoly, by far more dangerous then Microsoft ever was. The world has never seen anything like it. Therefore I ask my self where is this heading and what are the possible consequence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, I am researching alternative services I can use. The hub that brings most of the Google services together appears to be Google Contacts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It links Gmail, Google Calendar, Google Voice, Android etc and it appears to be the center of it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first application I will be testing is called &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.voxmobili.com/products/phonebook20/index.html&#34;&gt;Phonebook&lt;/a&gt;. The reason why Phonebook is the most promising I have found so far is, because it uses &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SyncML&#34;&gt;SyncML&lt;/a&gt;. SyncML is a platform independent information synchronization standard. That means I can sync my phonebook with all my other devices without being dependent on one single company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for my report and future steps.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
